Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Benjamin H. Wolf Additional Arbitration Files
1970-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolf, Benjamin H.
5539
45 cubic feet
45 linear ft.
Case files.
The collection includes arbitration awards, decisions, and related documents for cases arbitrated in the transportation, chemicals, clothing, retail food and retail trade, manufacturing, publishing, health care, bakery and confectionery, television, coal and oil, construction and electronics industries. Also, arbitration for various education and civil service agencies, primarily of the state of New York and New York City.
3811270
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 1986
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Arbitrator, labor mediator and attorney; visiting professor, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University. Wolf served as permanent arbitrator between the New York City Board of Education and the United Federation of Teachers; New York City and the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME); the New York City Off-Track Betting Corp. and AFSCME; New York State and AFSCME; the State University of New York and the Senate Professional Association; A. Goodman and the American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Union; and between the Simmons Company and the Upholsterers International Union. Wolf also served as impartial chairman for American Airlines and the Transport Workers Union of America; the men's shirt industry and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; and the Brooklyn Union Gas Company and the Transport Workers Union of America.
Born May 6, 1909. Attended Cornell University (B.A. 1930; LL.B. 1932).
Formerly labor mediator, New York State Board of Meidation; labor relations examiner, N.Y.S. Labor Relations Board.
Affiliated with National Academy of Arbitrators (board of governors 1971-; regional chairman 1967-1968); Industrial Relations Research Association; Society for Professionals in Dispute Resolution; New York Bar Association. On rosters of American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, National Mediation Board, New York State Board of Mediation, New Jersey State Board of Mediation, New York Public Employment Relations Board, New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission.
Arbitrator under contract for N.Y. City Board of Education and UFT; City of New York and District Council 37; OTB and DC37; N.Y. State and Council 82, AFSCME: State University of New York and Senate Professional Association; Metropolitan New York Milk Industry and IBT; New Rochelle Board of Education and UFT; A. Goodman & Sons and BCWU; Metropolitan Association of Optical Wholesalers and IUE; Simons Co. and Local 420, UIU.
Impartial Chairman; American Airlines and TWU, Men's Shirt Industry and ACWA; Brooklyn Union Gas and TWU; Williams Press and Pressmen's Union; Hiring Hall & Club Employees Union (Local 16); Westchester County Laundry Board of Trade and Local 335 IBT: Rochdale Village, Inc. and Local 90 Public Service Union; Ossining Board of Education and Ossining Teachers Association; Schwartz Laboratories, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers; Ross Oil Term. Corp., Howard Fuel Corp. & Local 365 UAW.
Scope and Contents
This volume is a continuation of the guide of arbitration case file records received from Mr. Wolf covering the period 1972-1982.
The collection is divided into 2 series. Series I (Boxes 1-38) include case files arranged by Mr. Wolf's assigned code numbers. Series II (Boxes 39-45) include other "miscellaneous" case files (code number not assigned) arranged alphabetically by company name.
This guide is indexed by issue and employer, as well as union name.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5305: Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5477: Benjamin Wolf Papers 5511: Benjamin Wolf Additional Papers 5803: Benjamin Wolf Additional Arbitration Files 6305: William B. Wolf Papers 6305 AV: William B. Wolf Audio-Visual 6305 P: William B. Wolf Photographs
Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Industrial relations -- New York (State); Industrial relations -- United States; Employee-management relations in government -- New York (State); Industrial arbitrators; Wolf, Benjamin H.,1909-
3811270
- 72-81 Schwerman Trucking Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 294, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  10/32/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Seniority.
- 72-82 Schweizer AirCraft Corp. vs. Local 1752 United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  1/3/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Seniority-Shift Transfers
- 72-83 Slant-Fin Corporation vs. Local 485 International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  11/24/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase.
- 72-84 Valhallia Board of Education vs. Valhallia Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  9/20/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay-Time Not Worked.
- 72-85 Valco Reproduction and Mailing vs. District 85, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  8/72. (No Award), Arbitrator's Notes, Routine Correspondence. Issue: Discharge.
- 72-86 Sealtest Food Corporation vs. Local 584 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  11/6/72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Layoff-Transfers.
- 72-87 The News vs. New York Typographical Union, No. 6, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  12/10/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Transfers- Temporary-Rates of Pay.
- 72-88 American Cyanamid Industry vs. Local III, International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  9/25/72. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 72-89 Ashland Chemical Corp. vs. Federal Labor Union 22026, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  12/4/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge-Improper Personal Conduct--Offensive Language.
- 72-90 Croton Board of Education vs. Croton Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  1/8/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Leaves of Absence
- 72-91 Livingston Manor Board of Education vs. Livingston Manor Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  11/16/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Workweek--Starting Time Change.
- 72-92 Clairol Inc. vs. Local 300 Cosmetics & Novelty Workers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1/22/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Shift Scheduling-Rotating Shifts
- 72-93 Kirrel Handbags, Inc. vs. Joint Board of New York, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  9/72. (No Award) Routine Correspondence. Postponed.
- 72-94 New York City Board of Education vs. United Federation of Teachers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  3/5/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties.
- 72-96 Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. Joint Local Executive Board of New Jersey, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  12/22/72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge-Insubordination
- Wilbur B. Driver Co. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  12/72. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 72-97 Lawrence Hose Company vs. Local 972 Textile Workers' Union of America (TWUA), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  11/72. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 72-98 Castle Coal and Oil Company vs. Local 239 Teamsters, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  11/21/72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge-- Insubordination
- 72-99 Dresser Industries, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America Local 1630, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1/9/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Evaluation of Job Factors.
- 72-100 Allied Aviation, Inc. vs. Local 504 Air Transport, Transport Workers' Union (TWU), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  11/17/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude--Interference with Production.
- 72-101 Home News Publishing Company vs. North New Jersey Newspaper Guild, Local 173, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  12/27/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Plant Rules--Moonlighting.
- 72-102 Bell Telephone Company-Pennsylvania vs. American Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  1/18/74. (No Award) Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Contracting Out--Temporary Employees.
- 72-103 Whitehead Brothers Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) Local 676, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  12/72. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 72-105 Coca Cola Bottling Company vs. IBT Local 177, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  2/12/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge-- Alcoholism--Drinking on the Job.
- 72-108 U.S. Metals Refinishing Company vs. United Steelworkers Local 837, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  1/30/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Overtime.
- 72-108 Deer Park Union Free School District #7 vs. Deer Park Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  1/3/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Seniority--Recall
- 72-109 Dresser Industries, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1630, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  2/5/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Failure to Schedule.
- 72-110 Quality Engraving vs. New York Lithographers and Photoengravers Union, Local 1, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  12/12/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Contract Interpretation--Lack of Work.
- 72-113 Merrick Board of Education vs. Merrick Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  1/73. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 72-114 Suffolk County vs. Suffolk County Civil Service Employees' Association (CSEA), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  3/9/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Meal Allowance.
- 72-115 New School for Social Research vs. Local 840 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  12/72. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 72-116 Jewish Hospital vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  3/21/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Sleeping on the Job
- 72-117 Half Hollow Board of Education vs. Half Hollow Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  3/21/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Workweek--Workday--Decrease.
- 72-118 City of New York vs. District Council #37, Local 1549, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1/25/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties.
- 72-120 Container Corporation of America vs. United Paperworkers, Local 520, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3a)
  4/23/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Overtime.
- 72-121 Port Washington School District vs. Port Washington Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  4/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Eligibility
- 72-122 Bailey Green and Elger vs. District 65 Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  1/3/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Leave of Absence--Reinstatement--Rates of Pay.
- 72-123 RCA Institutes vs. Faculty Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  9/73. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 72-124 New York City vs. Policemen's' Benevolent Association, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  12/72. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 72-125 Rensselaer City Schools vs. Rensselaer Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  2/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Assignment of Jobs.
- 72-126 Reuters Limited vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  3/19/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Error in Classification
- 72-127 New York City Off-Track Betting vs. Local 2021, District Council #37 American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees(AFSCME), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  3/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 73-1 Olin Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 609, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  7/30/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Refusal of Overtime.
- 73-2 Bayshore Union Free School District (UFSD) #4 vs. Bayshore Classroom Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  5/29/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Leaves of Absence.
- 73-3 Greater Amsterdam School District vs. Amsterdam Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  4/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Elimination of Jobs--Contract Interpretation.
- 73-4 Regina Corporation vs. Local 411 International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  4/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Equalization.
- 73-5 Maiden Mills, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers' Union of America, Local 506, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  2/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Seniority
- 73-6 Pratt Institute vs. Local 12, Security Officers, Guards, et. al, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  9/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-7 GAF Corporation vs. Local 227 International Chemical Workers' Union, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  8/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Seniority
- 73-8 B. F. Goodrich Company vs. Local 431 International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  1/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-9 Rome Hospital and Murphy Hospital vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Council 66, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  3/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Absences--Permissive.
- 73-10 Clifton Manufacturing Company vs. Textile Workers of America, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  7/22/74. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health and Welfare Programs
- 73-11 Jelrus Technical Product Corporation vs. Local 485, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  2/13/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Absences, Excessive
- 73-12 Scott Paper Company vs. Local 1, United Paperworkers International Union, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  4/30/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Transfer--Bumping.
- 73-13 Yonkers Board of Education vs. Yonkers Federation of Teachers, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  5/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Transfers--Seniority
- 73-14 Yonkers Board of Education vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  4/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Issue: Transfers
- 73-15 Dairylea Cooperative, Incorporated vs. Local 584 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  2/28/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 73-16 The Carborundum Company vs. Local 8-490 Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  1/73. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 73-17 City of Poughkeepsie vs. William Weiss, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  3/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, LD. Issue: Discipline--Discharge-- Incompetence-Misconduct
- 73-18 Petrie Stores Corporation vs. District 65 Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  5/17/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 73-19 Elmsford Board of Education vs. Elmsford Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  4/23/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Following Leave of Absence
- 73-20 Suffolk County Community College vs. Guild of Administrative Officers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  2/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Leaves of Absence--Contract Interpretation.
- 73-21 Carrier Corporation vs. Local 527 Sheet Metal Workers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  3/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 73-22 B. P. Oil Company vs. Local 8-337 Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers' International Union, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  5/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Assignment of Jobs--Seniority
- 73-23 Off Track Betting vs. District Council 37, Local 2120 American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  2/28/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Impasse--Fact Finding
- 73-24 Mack Molding Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1199, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  5/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Assignment of Jobs--Bargaining Unit Work.
- 73-25 Franklin Auto Body vs. Local 810 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  6/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 73-26 State of New York vs. Council 82 American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  4/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Suspension--Conviction of Crime
- 73-27 City of New York vs. Policemen's Benevolent Association, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  1/29/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Withdrawn
- 73-28 Beaunit Fibers, Division of Beaunit Corporation vs. Watauga Rayon Workers Union, Local 2207 United Textile Workers of America, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  6/12/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Drinking--Possession of Firearms; also: Lunch Periods; Assignment of Jobs.
- 73-29 Chalfonte Haddon Hall vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 508, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  8/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Walkout
- 73-30 Phelps Dodge Industries, Incorporated vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE) Local 437, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  3/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 73-31 American Standard, Incorporated vs. Pottery and Allied Workers Local 359, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  7/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Holiday Pay--Unexcused Absence.
- 73-32 ITT Continental Baking Company vs. Local 194 Bakery Drivers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  6/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents. Settled
- 73-33 City of White Plains vs. White Plains Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  3/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents. Settled
- 73-34 Hackensack Cable Corporation vs. Steelworkers Union Local 7418, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  8/27/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Pension Plan.
- 73-35 Jacques Kriesler Manufacturing Corporation vs. Local 147 Jewelry Workers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  4/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-36 John Stuart, Incorporated vs. United Storeworkers, Local 3 Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  7/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Retirement--Mandatory.
- 73-37 Borden, Incorporated vs. Local 1278 International Association of Machinists, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  7/24/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Insurance and Medical Plans
- 73-38 Interstate United Corporation vs. AMA Restaurant and Local 1, D.R.E.U., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  4/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 73-39 Brick Township Board of Education vs. Transport Workers Union Local 225, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  7/23/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contracting Out
- 73-40 Corning Glass Works vs. American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  11/14/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Duties Performed--Safety.
- 73-41 General Dynamics vs. Marine Draftsmen's Association, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  8/21/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Rates of Pay--Evaluation of Job Factors.
- 73-42 New York City Police Department vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association, Lieutenants Benevolent Association, and Detective Endowment Association, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  5/10/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacation--Computation.
- 73-43 New York City vs. Local 237 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  4/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-44 State University of New York (SUNY) vs. Senate Professional Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  5/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Mediation
- 73-45 LCR Manufacturing Division, Lanvin Charles of the Ritz vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 518, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  6/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, Exhibits. Issue: Standards of Production; Assignment of Jobs; Layoff--Seniority.
- 73-46 Allegri-Tech Incorporated vs. Associated Machine and Electric Workers, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  4/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-47 Anaconda Wire and Cable Company vs. Local 404 International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  4/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 73-48 Suffolk County vs. Suffolk County Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  8/15/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Time Not Worked.
- 73-49 Delta Airlines, Incorporated (on behalf of Northeast Airlines, Incorporated) vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)